This is Edison Carter,
coming to you very
much live and direct
on Network 23.
Carter's the best known reporter
we have on the air.
He satellites globally.
Where does all this
stuff come from, Bryce?
The components of Carter's mind.
M-M-Max, M-M-Max.
People translated as data.
It's computer-generated,
whatever it is.
It looks like Edison.
Max. Max Headroom.
Max?
He's a computer-generated
person based on you.
Two minds, but with
one single memory.
♪♪
♪ Sometimes I wonder
what I'm a-gonna do ♪
♪ There ain't no cure for
the summertime blues ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
This is Blank Reg, yeah.
Reg.
♪♪
Reg!
Dom, if it's not
loud, it doesn't work.
Are you tired of complaints
about sagging buns
or flat and naughty
little muffins?
Then this next
product is just for you.
And our first 23 callers
will receive, absolutely free,
this beautiful diamond necklace.
I don't know how you
can watch that drivel.
One of my little pleasures.
Makes me happy.
If you want the real
thing for the right stuff,
Zik-Zak muffin is it.
And the packaging is
perfect as a soiree purse.
You know, this home
shop-shop-shopping show is great.
From start to finish, it's just
sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell.
At last, a show with
no-no-no commercials.
Go away.
Reg, Max is ruining my program.
Good.
Honestly, someone at Network 23
ought to do something about him.
Reg.
Reg, come here.
Reg!
Ow! Bleeding hell, Dom,
nearly ripped me
bleeding ears off.
Come here.
Blimey, what is it?
Look.
Well, that's not Max, Dom.
It's those zippers again.
They must have
a hell of a setup.
Zipping into network
transmissions takes a lot of power.
Well, they're
ruining my shopping.
Takes a lot of nerve as well.
How are they doing this?
Well, you see, they hack
into our satellite transponders
and they hijack our frequency.
Ashwell, Lauren means how
are they cracking our security?
Oh.
They flatten our ratings
every time they zip us like that.
Look at those figures.
Shoppin' Spree TV is diving.
Viewers won't stand for this.
This has got to be stopped.
This is dangerous.
If they can break into
our carrier that easily,
nothing's safe.
Our bank accounts,
our medical records.
Never mind that.
What about ratings?
I've already
alerted Bryce Lynch.
He's been trying to
track them for some time.
He was a hacker
himself, you know.
Send a thief to catch a thief.
Ah, Bryce.
You get that last zipping?
Of course.
I've isolated the satellite
they're hacking into.
Now, it wasn't easy, because
they hacked our security...
Bryce, just the
conclusion will be fine.
The conclusion, Mr. Cheviot,
is that they are extremely good.
But not as good
as I am, naturally.
Would you like to
watch my endgame?
He thinks this is a game.
He thinks everything's a game.
Don't you, Bryce?
Yes. I often play chess
with the 23 computer.
And I often beat it.
Ah, here we go. Would
you like to watch?
You've got it.
Well done, Bryce.
Uh, I think there's
a little error.
Can you hang on just one minute?
There's your target.
That's it, Mr. Cheviot.
You've got your zipper.
Let me have security.
You're tuned to
Big-Time Television.
Where music is the
brandy of the damned.
So, let's pop the cork on this.
Go, go, go.
Hold on, Dominique,
he just walked in.
You see what that explosion
did to the people in that city,
you'll know why they
call it a breeder reactor.
Edison, it's Dominique.
Blank Reg has been arrested.
What happened?
Metrocops. They said
he was signal zipping.
Reg? That's crazy.
That's way out of his league.
Reg asked me to call you.
Edison, you've got to help him.
Where are they holding him?
Metro jail 42.
I'm on my way.
Insert credit tube.
Now, just tell me the truth.
Were you zipping into Network
23 transmissions from Big-Time?
Do me a favor, girl.
There's not enough power in
that bus to zip up me trousers,
never mind a network satellite.
I don't think you understand
the severity of this charge.
Network zipping
is a prime offense.
- Sir.
- I understand
one thing, darling.
Someone's trying to frame me.
And when I find who,
I'm gonna unilaterally
murder the swine.
Watch your threats.
We are being monitored.
Now, we might have a chance,
as long as you
aren't a recidivist.
Me? No way.
I can't even spell it.
You don't have
a criminal profile?
That's right.
Of course I don't.
Edison, you've got
to get me out of this.
Someone is setting
me up. Right up.
All rise for the most
highly rated judge.
Please approach the bench.
Your honor, the network
has reason to believe
that an indictment
of first-degree zipping
should be brought
against this defendant.
Counsel for the defense.
I move for dismissal
on the grounds
that the network has no
first-hand corroboration
that my client
committed this crime.
He's a Blank, your honor.
A Blank?
In that case,
he's beyond my jurisprudence.
Video court.
But you haven't
evaluated my floppy disc.
The charges stand.
We've got to pick a court date.
Would you care to do the honors?
No thanks.
All yours.
I play Grateful Dead
on Wednesdays.
It only gives me one day
to prepare your defense.
You believe me,
don't you, old son?
Yeah. You didn't, you
couldn't, and you wouldn't.
Question is, who did?
How's Reg?
He's pretty angry, all right.
What you got?
Well, Bryce coordinated
the targeting for that raid.
It seems he had a problem
and it switched from mid-set,
which is very strange.
Can it be switched?
Yeah, it could, but why?
Okay, the sat cam program
produces a lot of temporary files.
Then discards them.
All those bits and pieces
go into the purge directory,
which is a sort of
electronic trash bin.
- Mm-hmm.
- Which the systems operator
empties at the end of the day.
Everything ends up in there.
Discarded files, bits and
pieces of video outtakes,
messages.
I'll see what I can find.
Praying, Bryce?
No.
No need, huh?
Oh, good. Oh, good.
Game of chess?
No thanks, Max.
You can be white.
No thanks, Max, really.
I'm thinking.
I'm evaluating a
recent strategy.
I know.
Did it work?
What?
Switching the coordinates.
How on earth did you know?
I happened to be flit-flit-flitting
about the mainframe
and I just watched the show.
You won't tell.
Will you?
These files write over themselves
a lot before they're thrown away.
I'll get the computer
to extrapolate it for us.
Now, those are the
coordinates of the target.
But look, they switch
and give us another set.
What are the new coordinates?
Big-Time Television.
What are the
original coordinates?
I'm beginning to get a very
nasty tingle in my spine.
Well, that's good.
Probably means a story.
It's not nice to
eavesdrop, Murray.
It's not nice to falsify
evidence, either.
Let's have the coordinates.
My God, it's ACS.
The Academy of
Computer Sciences.
Now, that is a story.
Network 23's computer wiz
kids zipping their own channel?
That's a story, all right.
Yeah, I get your point.
A bit sensitive.
Sensitive? You
can say that again.
All right. Go to ACS.
Lay some story on them,
see just what's going on.
Murray, Bryce Lynch on line two.
Yeah.
- Theora.
- It'll be fun, Edison.
Like going back to school.
- Theora.
- What?
We both know something
else about ACS, don't we?
Yes, we do.
It's where Bryce came from.
We got a problem.
Listen, I have a great idea.
I just told Bryce
to go with you.
You see, he'll be
able to talk to the kids,
help you subvert
the little geniuses.
What's the matter?
What is the matter?
Well?
Well what?
W-Well, as they said
to K-K-King Charles I
on the scaffold,
are you-are you
going to go quietly?
Or do you need a push?
To ACS?
Murray asked me to.
I have to help Edison.
What could I say?
I have no choice.
Of course-Of course
you have a choice.
The same one Charles I had.
Exactly.
Will you come with me?
I think I have a problem.
Academy of Computer
Sciences fourth period pod begins
in exactly 1 minute
and 3.0 seconds.
Your assignment for this
period is to compute ten designs
for peizo polymer fingers
of a surgical robot hand.
Also, please note that
we have distinguished
visitors from Network 23 today.
So please show them
how courteous we are.
The spore is loaded.
You take the first watch.
Look here, that's me.
Oh, yeah. You trying to
tell me you had sideburns?
Yeah.
This bring back memories?
Some.
Most memories are
the random retrieval
of normally superfluous data.
A waste of real time.
I try to bulk erase mine daily.
Yeah, well, be careful
you don't erase all the bits
that add up to experience.
Oh, I keep the
critical material.
I remember my first
undergraduate day here.
It was Tuesday. It was
raining, and I was cold.
Huh. Your random recall
is almost as good as Max'.
Oh, that's not random.
That was my tenth birthday.
They've separated.
These kids are bright.
They're into
securicams everywhere.
I mean, I'm tapping
off their illicit feeds.
Which makes you even brighter.
- Older.
- Wiser.
Marry me, Murray.
Announcement.
Nanotechnology pod test results
are posted in the sub-micron
lab for your viewing.
Headsysop.
Does it teach or devour maidens?
Announcement. Students
are reminded not to leave
their mutated molecules
in their lockers overnight.
Well, we haven't got
any absolute proof.
But the signals were
tracked to this campus.
Naturally, I'm more
inquisitive than anything else.
Naturally.
Are you positive about this?
One of your former
students did the tracking.
Bryce Lynch. And he
claims to be a genius, so...
Ah, Lynch. Excellent student.
Single-minded. Well,
ACS students don't
make mistakes,
and Lynch was
one of the very best.
In his time, of course.
Odd boy.
He never made contact with
his parents after he came to us.
They were middle
management, you know.
I well remember...
Time for my 3:00 pod.
I'll bring this up
after session.
I'm as anxious as you
to get to the bottom of it.
Headsysops, pods.
Tell you, in my day, it was
headmasters and classes.
Yes, yes. How times change.
We're all input
systems, operators,
and pod managers now, my boy.
But you can't fool and
old head, you know.
Settle down, settle
down. Order from chaos.
And now, for your next project,
you will each receive a package
containing one floppy diskette,
an old-fashioned 888 processor,
and a coat hanger.
With these materials, you will
be expected to design a device
to snare Clifford here.
We'll see which one of you
can build the better mousetrap.
- Piece of cake.
- Piece of cheese.
Your humor parameters
need expanding, Nicholas.
Yes, Stratton?
Can we kill it?
Yes, that is within the
bounds of the experiment.
But I'm afraid you'll find that
more difficult than you imagine.
Uh, Miss Partridge?
What are the time
parameters here?
You may have until
the end of the day.
If there are no
further questions...
Yes, Stratton?
What's Edison Carter doing here?
Oh, once again my
little code crunchers
are getting ahead
of their old sysop.
Say hello to Mr. Edison Carter.
Hello, Mr. Carter.
He does look like Max Headroom.
Uh, no, actually.
He looks like me.
Mr. Carter brings a
disturbing piece of information.
He suspects some
highly illegal signal zipping
has been emanating
from this campus.
Now, if this is true,
I expect the responsible
party to report to my office.
Because you are all minors,
you will be spared the
particular punishment
usually afforded adults.
As I am fond of saying,
we have our own methods.
Pod dismissed.
They seem like a
normal bunch of kids.
- Oh, yes.
- Homicidal rodent squishers.
You really expect
the guilty party
just to march right
into your office?
Of course. We
instill the morality
of binary absolutes
here, Mr. Carter.
The useful
consequence of pure logic
is the divine simplicity of a
yes/no decision about everything.
Well, what about
right and wrong?
I notice you said
"responsible party," not "guilty."
A gray area is quite useless
to a computer specialist.
We don't deal in guilt.
We deal in information.
That is why the appropriate
party will be with us shortly.
You will see.
Let's adjourn to my office.
Doesn't this place bring
back f-f-fond memories, Bryce?
Ah-Ah-Ah, the sounds,
the s-s-squeak of
trainers on the gym floor,
the screech of
ch-chalk on gallium chip.
The secret kiss behind
the computer terminal.
It wasn't like that.
Why do people get so
sentimental about college days?
Because for
p-p-people like Edison,
it was a time of
giggles, g-g-girls, guys,
and g-g-getting into trouble.
- Not me.
- Not yet.
Bryce Lynch is in there.
Well, it's Bryce Lynch.
We got the warning.
Good. How's your security?
Optimized. Only the
inner circle knows.
What's that?
My computer regeneration
project. Max Headroom.
Ah, yes. We've heard about that.
Rather primitive.
We're into cross-species
regeneration these days.
A little more advanced.
Se-Se-Se...
Seems like a nice boy.
Nicholas rather enjoys
his performances.
Talk-Talk-Talking
of performances,
if you're gonna get us
out of this m-m-mess
you got us into, you'll
need some fancy dancing.
What puzzles me is
how a former student
could have been incorrect
about ACS being the
source of the zipping.
Bryce wasn't wrong.
The party who did it
just isn't 'fessing up.
Logically impure.
It would assume that
there is a guilty party.
It just doesn't compute.
It would imply a gray area.
Not at ACS, Mr. Carter.
We work with
perfect information.
Paradise, huh?
Well, maybe you got a
dragon in the Garden of Eden.
You mind if I have a
look around on my own?
No, no, not at all.
But, Mr. Carter,
beware the dragon.
- How's Fang?
- Off his food.
Blimey, that bad?
Now, be sure he gets
his ice cream every night.
Yes, I will, but he won't eat
it out of your spoon for me.
And Big-Time is off air.
We could go out of business.
He likes chocolate chip best.
If they are zipping, Theora,
they're very
clever at hiding it.
Apart from the
inside of locker doors,
- whole place is clean.
- Oh, no, it isn't, Edison.
That hardware they've got in there
is fully capable of signal zipping.
Look.
Crafty little devils.
That's nothing to
the rest of the setup.
Some have
perverted little minds.
Oh, good, there's Bryce.
Nice to see you accessing
the old memory bank, sir.
Turn down the potentiometer
before you close the mic.
I've come to say goodbye.
We're about finished here.
Are your mics security looped?
- Of course.
- Good.
Congratulations.
We got away with it.
The only thing that can
happen to Blank Reg now
is some temporary discomfort.
They'll soon find out he
hasn't the power to zip
and justice will compute.
- Eventually.
- You little beast.
Bryce. I don't believe it.
Lots of little girls' and
boys' tricks in the system.
What kind of games
did you play, Theora?
Growing up games.
Doctors and nurses.
Yeah, well, there's
nothing like a good physical.
Okay, turn left and
go straight ahead
until you reach the stairwell.
Learn anything that
might brighten my day?
Yes, I was quite fast.
At the top of the
stairs, turn left
and then down the hall.
Ah. I must remember to
try and catch up with you.
- As a specialist?
- But of course.
Now I want you to lift
the nose of the statue.
Pardon?
You lift the nose,
you flip the switch,
and the door behind
the statue opens.
I'm afraid Bryce has
been a very naughty boy.
I wonder what you
tweak to close it.
Well, Bryce, I wondered
what had happened to you.
What you up to?
Sneaking a smoke? Or...
zipping a network?
Edison, how did you get in here?
I think we better
go have a little talk.
Oh, and try and remember,
I was a kid once too.
I wish you hadn't
kept anything from me.
- Like what?
- Your record.
But he hasn't got a
record. He's a Blank.
Previous criminal activities.
They can't have any files on me.
I've been off the
records for years.
The network police ran
a computer investigation.
They say the probability is
you committed these crimes.
Oh, probability.
Yes, Dominique.
If the probability computes,
and in cases where
there's no evidence,
they work on the probability.
Well, I expect it saves
everybody a lot of work.
It's not gonna save you, Reg.
You compute.
And the punishment for
network program zipping
is terminal.
You put together pieces
of my sat cam sequence
from the purge directory?
Most of it. The
computer did the rest.
Man. I gotta recode
that sat cam program
to wipe out all the files
before dumping them.
We saw how you altered the
target from ACS to Big-Time.
Computer-enhanced files.
Illegally obtained.
You can't use that
against me, Edison.
That's inadmissible evidence.
We don't want to use
anything against you, Bryce.
- We want to help Reg. So should you.
- Why?
Because you've put him
in very serious danger.
Bryce, I'm getting angry.
Then stop. It's
quite unnecessary.
Blank Reg didn't zip
our transmissions, right?
You know he didn't.
Why did you do it?
I mean, why Reg, of all people?
I had to make a quick decision.
I had to protect ACS, didn't I?
I don't believe it. An emotion.
A decision, Edison.
I simply selected the closest
option that would achieve that goal.
Now, Blank Reg couldn't be
proven guilty. It's an optimum solution.
What about right and wrong?
Non-empirical concepts.
Don't you understand? The network court
wants to make an example of someone.
And Reg is it.
Network courts.
Our courts.
All we have to do is
rearrange the information.
As long as no one
finds out about ACS.
Bryce, stop treating
people like machines.
You can't rearrange
information which is evidence.
Grow up.
Okay, okay, so you were right.
He is an obstinate little child.
Where are you going, Edison?
Cheviot's office.
Maybe I can get him to fix
things with the network court.
You're just like Bryce.
- What?
- Fix things with the court.
- I mean, what about Reg?
- I care about Reg.
What about justice? You don't
need to fix it. He didn't do it.
But how do we
prove he didn't do it?
Bryce is right.
We can't use the
information he accessed
and we can't testify for Reg.
As 23's employees, our evidence
is inadmissible in 23's court.
Unless Bryce helps,
Reg is in very real trouble.
Well, I'm gonna go and see Reg.
I mean, there must be a way
of proving he's incapable
of zipping from Big-Time.
If Bryce won't help, I will.
Why are you smirking
at me like that?
Me? Smirk?
That's not in my
pro-pro-program.
I thought you were on my side.
It's not a ques-question
of sides anymore, Bryce.
Ha ha. Except
for the right side.
I'm uncharacteristically
confused.
I'm used to logic, not opinion.
The thing... The thing
is you're a bit like me.
Ex-Except we've
got different bits.
Sometimes I think I
could use some leg-legs,
and right now I think you-you-you
could use some conscience.
Which file is it in?
Think of yourself
as a human program
and that bit of you has
developed a glitch-ch-ch.
Developed a glitch.
Everyone keeps
lecturing me these days.
That's why I'm just
talk-talk-t-talking to you
about getting
Blank Reg released.
I know.
Yes, sir. That's right, sir.
We dropped off three more.
Leave the truck
around the loading dock.
If you told your lawyer
about your criminal profile,
she might have been better
prepared to defend you.
I told you, Dom, I didn't know.
How could you not know
you had a criminal profile?
It's something called
the Career Capability
Malfeasance Program.
CPMP.
It's the program that matches
Blanks with unassigned profiles.
It compares the crime template
to the personality template.
And if it matches,
you're assumed guilty.
Criminals can blank
out their identities,
but they can't get rid
of their criminal profile.
Are you saying there
are more criminal profiles
than there are criminals?
Precisely.
If a Blank is arrested now,
they run a CPMP on him.
If the computer says the
probability is high enough,
it's considered a match.
So that isn't
really your profile.
That's what I've been trying
to tell you. Blimey, Dom.
Isn't science wonderful?
- Oh, Reg.
- Yeah, wonderfully inhuman.
I'm gonna go to 23.
Our only chance is to
get Murray to authorize
this as a story.
Template matching isn't justice.
It's just administrative
convenience.
Administrators. Button pushers.
Hold on, Reg.
As they say, the last resort of
the innocent is always publicity.
Watch me.
Nicholas.
We need a real-time conference.
What's tickling your synapses?
Now look. In my day, zipping
used to be a good hack.
But things have changed.
It's a criminal offense now.
And by trying to protect you
and ACS, I'm in conflict
with my own network.
So?
So flatline the project
and submit a
report to your sysop.
That's not a winning option.
You're a minor. They
won't do anything to you.
They'll dump me from
the Academy, Bryce.
Look, as long as
nobody says anything,
nobody gets in trouble.
Blank Reg does.
Who? That guy?
He's just an old Blank.
But he didn't do it.
We both know that.
That's irrelevant.
Is this what happens
when you have to work
around computer illiterates?
You're really not compiling
this, are you, Nicholas?
You did it. Blank
Reg didn't. Facts.
Give me credit, Bryce.
I've got it all worked out.
I'm sure your procedures
are impeccable.
But you're using
the wrong formula.
You remind me of myself.
Should I take that
as a compliment?
No.
Calm down, Reg. I'm sure
Miss Keeler is on her way.
If she's late for
my trial, I'll kill her.
All homicide threats are
recorded for later playback.
Stick that in your pipe
and smoke it, sunshine.
Bryce.
I'm at the Academy.
I just had a real-time conference
with the zipping hacker.
- Nicholas.
- That's wonderful.
No, it's not.
It didn't work.
I don't know what to
do, Theora. Help me.
What is it?
We just found out who
the guest prosecutor is.
Paul Wade?
But he's the frontman for
23's You the Jury show.
And the best television
prosecutor money can buy.
It's a game show for my life.
Welcome to Network 23's
award-winning game show
You the Jury.
This is the defendant,
Blank Reg, a pirate TV operator
employed by Big-Time Television,
who Network 23 has charged
with first-degree signal zipping.
These are the Metrocops who
claim they caught Blank Reg in the act.
And this is the TV pirate's
attorney, Shelley Keeler.
Shelley's got her
work cut out for her,
because today's guest prosecutor
is the Channel of Fortune's
leading quiz master,
Paul Wade.
On the show where the
audience decides the verdict,
You the Jury.
We'll be back with our first
pleading in just a moment,
but first, this word.
If you want to do
justice to your cooking,
try Zik-Zak Soy Muffin Mix.
Tasteless, colorless,
and odorless.
The perfect base
for every taste.
Don't be guilty that
they have no taste.
I know, Mr. Cheviot,
but Edison insisted.
All right, Murray, put him on.
Yes, Carter.
Your network court is on the
verge of convicting an innocent man.
That's an awfully serious
charge. Can you back it up?
I can.
But I need you to buy
me a little more time.
Are you asking me to subvert
the network's judicial process?
Quite the contrary.
I believe the true source of
the zipping is not Blank Reg,
but the Academy of
Computer Sciences.
For God's sake, Edison,
those youngsters represent
the distillation of human intellect.
They're the root
stock of the future.
Bryce Lynch is
the product of ACS.
And Bryce is covering this
up by changing the coordinates
away from the true
source of the zipping.
If that's true, if our own head
of research and development
is responsible for
covering up a crime
which cost this network
hundreds of thousands of credits,
we'll be the laughingstock
of the industry.
We could lose the
entire Zik-Zak account.
Mr. Cheviot, couldn't we
reschedule the network court?
Give Edison some time
to clean up this mess.
Please. Sir, the
accused is Blank Reg.
I'm sorry about Blank
Reg, believe me.
If he's innocent, I'm
sure he'll be acquitted.
He's only one man.
I have to concern myself
with the greatest good
for the greatest
number of people.
Which means this entire network.
No, Murray. I won't reschedule.
Better find Bryce.
It's time for kill or cure.
Welcome back to You the Jury.
And now, here's the judge.
Thank you. Hello, hello, hello.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
And welcome to the
show that puts you
in the jury box.
Our first case today
involves a charge of zipping
against a Blank Reg.
For 1,000 credits, how does
your client plead, Ms. Keeler?
Innocent. I...
I mean, not guilty, sir.
Just relax, Ms. Keeler.
Proceed with your opening
argument, Mr. Wade.
Thanks, Bob.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
prosecution intends to prove
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that the Blank known as Reg
is guilty of network zipping.
What we're really talking
about here is principle.
What we're talking about
is a threat to television.
To our lives.
We are talking
about interruptioning.
When decent, honest,
peaceful television-loving people
cannot watch Shoppin' Spree
without these savage attacks
on their viewing freedom,
we have to ask this question.
Are we being too lenient?
When our wives and daughters
cannot shop from their
own homes in peace,
we must ask is consumerism
itself under attack?
Credit for your thoughts.
Save your money, Edison.
You already know.
I don't want to sound paranoid,
but...
I know this place is bugged.
Now we're in a cone of silence.
No one can eavesdrop.
I tried to redirect Nicholas,
but he's a poorly
designed system.
What system?
The system that allows him to
be better off by keeping quiet.
I mean, what good is a system
if it doesn't work properly?
I hate to be the one to
break this to you, Bryce,
but life is more than just
interactive systems analysis.
Not really.
It's a matter of information.
Once we understand and
collate our ideas, life will be
much simpler, really.
It's a matter of
number crunching.
It's not just more complicated.
Look, life is based on
something more than just logic.
It's based on...
feelings.
So everyone keeps telling me.
Is it difficult to keep
your feelings at bay?
Well, you can
switch them off when
they become inconvenient.
It's just that every time you do,
you become a byte less human.
But what if a microchip
failed to work properly
because it had to make a moral
decision every time it switched?
Okay.
And what if you created
an artificial intelligence
and it wouldn't work because it
disagreed with your principles?
Then you have a choice which is
not just a yes/no binary absolute.
It's a question of conscience.
Yeah.
Conscience.
Better work that one out.
Look,
I really enjoyed this little
chat, but I gotta get going.
I gotta go watch a friend of mine
go down for something he didn't do.
Well, at least you'll
understand that.
So, my little ch-ch-chip
off the old mainframe,
what are you going to do?
Well,
I think I need to rewrite
my own program.
Okay. Now, moving on to our
second round of questioning.
Oh, that's the
plea-bargaining buzzer.
Approach the bench, guys.
According to our
rolling audience poll,
the Blank Reg should be
reduced to random electrons
by a margin of 9 to 1.
This is my first and
last offer, sweetheart.
If the Blank cops to zipping,
I'll settle for life and a day.
I have to confer with my client.
Will she go for
the life and a day,
or try to get the Blank free?
Let's ask some of the folks
in the gallery what they think.
- This is the deal.
- I understand the offer.
If I confess to
something I didn't do,
I go to prison for
the rest of me life.
Stuff it. I'd make a
very bad prisoner.
They used the phrase
random electrons.
I can't spell that, either.
It means no?
Conference time's up.
Approach the bench.
So, what'll it be, Shelley?
We're gonna go for it.
Oh, they're gonna go for it.
Nicholas. You've been cheating.
Nice try.
Cheating?
Loading inaccurate information
designed to crash
a logic program.
And output bias to produce
selective information.
And putting it
simply, Nick, lying.
We couldn't.
The coordinates are clear.
It really was the Big-Time
bus the zipping came from.
Blank Reg must be brilliant.
And guilty.
Hey, let's watch his sentencing.
Blank Reg, eh?
Fancy being able
to zip a live program.
Bryce, you're making a
mistake in your old age.
You can't tell one set of
coordinates from another.
I assumed you guys had learned
something since I was here,
but it's evident
that your generation
hasn't the skills nor
the system for zipping.
What would you call this setup?
Toys for Tots.
You're taking credit
for Reg's achievement.
You're obviously trying
to impress the girls.
Say when, Mr. Lynch.
Nicholas, you're
behaving emotionally.
Shut up.
You wouldn't dare.
Jury find Blank...
I move for dismissal.
Hold it. Looks like we've
got a move for dismissal.
- On what grounds, Ms. Keeler?
- Pure logic.
My client, Blank Reg, couldn't possibly
have caused the zipping you just saw.
He's here in the court.
Oh.
Dismissed.
Oh, Dom, that's the first time
you've ever had
your arms around me.
Oh, Reggie, darling.
Ugh, about your
personal hygiene.
Oh.
What made Bryce change his mind?
He didn't. He adjusted
his parameters.
Think it'll make him
any easier to work with?
Never. Con-Con-Converts
are the worst kind of bigots.
One of yours?
One of my best.
Closed-Captioned By J.R.
Media Services, Inc. Burbank, CA